{"1": {"question": "What period of composition does Chopin represent?", "correct": "Romantic", "incorrect": ["Baroque", "Classical", "Impressionist"]}, "2": {"question": "What period of composition does Schumann represent?", "correct": "Romantic", "incorrect": ["Baroque", "Classical", "Impressionist"]}, "3": {"question": "What period of composition does Debussy represent?", "correct": "Impressionist", "incorrect": ["Baroque", "Classical", "Romantic"]}, "4": {"question": "Which of the following clefs is used by the Bassoon?", "correct": "Bass", "incorrect": ["Treble", "Percussion", "Alto"]}, "5": {"question": "Which of the following clefs is used by the Bassoon?", "correct": "Tenor", "incorrect": ["Treble", "Percussion", "Alto"]}, "6": {"question": "Which of the following clefs is used by the Clarinet?", "correct": "Treble", "incorrect": ["Bass", "Tenor", "Alto"]}, "7": {"question": "What (written) note represents the bottom of the range of the Bassoon?", "correct": "B flat", "incorrect": ["E flat", "C", "G"]}, "8": {"question": "What (written) note represents the top of the range of the Bassoon?", "correct": "G", "incorrect": ["B flat", "C", "E flat"]}, "9": {"question": "What (written) note represents the bottom of the range of the Clarinet?", "correct": "E", "incorrect": ["C", "H", "E flat"]}, "10": {"question": "What (written) note represents the top of the range of the Clarinet?", "correct": "C", "incorrect": ["E flat", "B flat", "G"]}, "11": {"question": "What (written) note represents the bottom of the range of the Flute?", "correct": "C", "incorrect": ["D", "E", "B flat"]}, "12": {"question": "What (written) note represents the top of the range of the Flute?", "correct": "D", "incorrect": ["C", "E", "B flat"]}, "13": {"question": "What (written) note represents the bottom of the range of the Oboe?", "correct": "B flat", "incorrect": ["A", "C", "F"]}, "14": {"question": "What (written) note represents the top of the range of the Oboe?", "correct": "A", "incorrect": ["B flat", "E", "G"]}, "15": {"question": "Which type of piece was prominent within Chopin's compositional oeuvre (body of work)?", "correct": "Etude", "incorrect": ["Symphony", "Chamber", "Impromptu"]}, "16": {"question": "Which type of piece was prominent within Schumann's compositional oeuvre (body of work)?", "correct": "Symphony", "incorrect": ["Etude", "Impromptu", "Sonata"]}, "17": {"question": "Which type of piece was prominent within Debussy's compositional oeuvre (body of work)?", "correct": "Suite", "incorrect": ["Etude", "Sonata", "Symphony"]}, "18": {"question": "How is music written for Clarinet in A sounded?", "correct": "3 semitones lower", "incorrect": ["3 semitones higher", "2 tones lower", "2 tones higher"]}, "19": {"question": "Which of the following types of pieces does not form a substantial part of Chopin's composition:", "correct": "Symphony", "incorrect": ["Etude", "Impromptu", "Nocturne"]}, "20": {"question": "Which of the following types of pieces does not form a substantial part of Debussy's composition:", "correct": "Nocturne", "incorrect": ["Opera", "Sonata", "Clair de Lune"]}, "21": {"question": "Which of the following types of pieces does not form a substantial part of Schumann's composition:", "correct": "Fugue", "incorrect": ["Lieder", "Orchestral music", "Chamber"]}, "22": {"question": "Name a characteristic of Chopin's compositional style.", "correct": "Dissonance", "incorrect": ["12-tone serialism", "Minimalism", "Vocoding"]}, "23": {"question": "Name a characteristic of Debussy's compositional style.", "correct": "Non-traditional scales and tonal structures", "incorrect": ["Monophony", "Alliteration", "Alberti bass"]}, "24": {"question": "Name a characteristic of Schumann's compositional style.", "correct": "Strong rhythmic patterns", "incorrect": ["Dissonance", "Minimalism", "Basso ostinato"]}, "25": {"question": "What is an auxiliary instrument?", "correct": "A 'non-standard' version of the common members of an instrumental family", "incorrect": ["A supporting instrument in an ensemble", "An instrument made out of wood", "All of the above"]}, "26": {"question": "Which of the following is not typically found in an orchestra?", "correct": "The Contrabass Clarinet", "incorrect": ["The Bass Clarinet", "The Bb Clarinet", "The Flute"]}, "27": {"question": "Which of the following composers was not from the Romantic era?", "correct": "Debussy", "incorrect": ["Chopin", "Schumann", "Liszt"]}, "28": {"question": "Which of the following composers was not from the Impressionist era?", "correct": "Chopin", "incorrect": ["Debussy", "Ravel", "Verdi"]}, "29": {"question": "Which of the following composers was from the Impressionist era?", "correct": "Debussy", "incorrect": ["Chopin", "Schumann", "Liszt"]}, "30": {"question": "Who wrote 21 nocturnes?", "correct": "Chopin", "incorrect": ["Debussy", "Bach", "Joe Biden"]}}